motherhoodonadime.com 2018-02-08

# Privacy Policy - Kids Activities | Saving Money | Home Management | Motherhood on a Dime

Privacy Policy for [www.motherhoodonadime.com](http://www.overwhelmedcouponmom.com/)

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at motherhoodonadime @ gmail . com.  
At Motherhood on a Dime (MOAD), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by MOAD and how it is used.  
****

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, MOAD makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol(IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
MOAD does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on MOAD.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to MOAD and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Our advertising partners include …….

Commission Junction

Amazon

Linkshare

Share-A-Sale

Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

MOAD has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. MOAD’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
